Enter Kratos Core: An autonomous, AI-driven asset management engine built natively for the Mantle Network.
We are not just building another yield aggregator.
We are building a fully autonomous hedge fund that operates with zero human emotion and strict institutional guardrails.
At the heart of Kratos is our dual-LLM architecture.
A custom Python ingestion daemon continuously pulls live macroeconomic data.
Gemini 3.5 Flash serves as our Chief Investment Officer, synthesizing global liquidity and risk sentiment into a macro thesis.
This thesis is immediately handed off to Mistral 7B, our quantitative structurer,
which translates the sentiment into precise mathematical allocations across three premium Mantle assets:
Ondo U.S. Dollar Yield for baseline stability, staked ether for liquid staking yield, and fBTC for macro Bitcoin exposure.
But AI hallucinates. How do we trust it with capital?
We don't. Before any transaction is signed,
our execution engine forces the AI's proposed allocations through hard-coded, zero-trust institutional guardrails.
It actively verifies OFAC compliance, enforces strict maximum drawdowns, and limits volatility caps.
Only if every single security constraint passes does the agent cryptographically sign the payload
and broadcast it directly to our custom Solidity Vault on the Mantle testnet.
No human intervention. Zero mock data. Everything is verifiable on-chain.
To bridge the gap between AI autonomy and human oversight, we built a premium React telemetry dashboard.
Investors can monitor Total Value Locked, track live allocations,
and watch the AI Awakening Stream, a raw, real-time terminal feed of the agent's internal reasoning,
compliance checks, and live Mantle transaction hashes.
Kratos Core outpaces manual risk management, bringing transparency to DeFi.